Hello everyone.
Tim and Melinda are running late.
But we have a lot to get through.
So we should get started.
Jason, can you please take the minutes today?
Yes, of course, Tony.
No problem.
Thanks.
Okay, let's get the ball rolling.
First on the agenda today,
Carrie, can you please give us an update
on the marketing strategy for our new beverage ginger cola?
Yes, Tony.
Well, we have decided to pitch the new ginger cola
as a health and energy drink.
Fantastic.
I think this will be our next big hit.
There is no reason that it shouldn't be a winner.
It tastes great.
It's healthy.
And it has very low calories.
It's perfect for working out.
Let's make this the next red bull energy drink.
Where are we with the advertising and promotion strategy?
We still have a few things to work out.
But we are planning to have a power hitter
from the Japan baseball league as a celebrity endorsement.
We still have to iron out some details.
But we think he's a great fit.
Great idea.
Well, let's set aside more time at the next meeting.
For a more in-depth look at what you have planned.
Of course, that's really important.
But we have a lot to cover in today's meeting.
Okay, Tony.
I will be ready to present to everyone then.
Let's move on to the next topic.
I have sent around an action list for each of you to take a look at.
It includes a look at the following calls to action
that we need to address for the upcoming charity walkathon.
Let's take a few moments and go over everyone's role.
This is extremely important for us.
We need to give back to the community.
I couldn't agree more.
This has been at the top of all our agendas.
And we have come up with some pretty innovative ideas.
Let me start things off.
If that's okay with everyone else.